You know, you're just like, is everything a conspiracy?
And then you're like, yes, actually.
And I say that in the sense that it's not conspiracy theory.
It feels like conspiracy if you believe that the powers that be have your best interests at heart.
So if that is your grounding foundational belief, then anything challenging that feels like conspiracy.
Which is why, like, when people say, like, the system isn't broken, it's working the way it's supposed to.
Flips a switch for a lot of people because you're like, oh, you know, like you think, dang, why is there so many cop shows and military shows?
And you're like, I'm bugging.
And then you find out that there's actually CIA involvement and FBI involvement in the movies that get made and how they get made.
And then you understand that oligarchs are running newspapers because it's not about an artistic mandate.
It's about a money mandate.
And that money mandate is often determined by people who may not necessarily every time say we're going to do this because we don't like black people.
However, they may willingly say, well, those guys did it and they didn't like black people and they made a lot of money off of it.
And I mean, I couldn't care less, but I want to make money, so I'll do it, too.
And I'll do it, too.